

Galpothugodage Don Akalanka Kavinda Perera

Software Engineer

PROFILE

June 7th 2002

C

+94763410607

 \searrow

akalankaperera128@gmail.com

in

https://www.linkedin.com/in/akalanka-perera-50899a1b3

https://akalanka47000.github.io/portfolio/

ABOUT ME

A twenty year old, highly motivated software engineer fluent in programming as well as designing, adept to quick learning and sharp reconnaissance. I'm eager to explore new fields and always dependable when it comes to getting quality work done on time.

SKILLS

VueJS NodeJS NextJS **Flutter** Laravel Angular **NestJS Spring Boot** Firebase MongoDB **MySQL** Gitlab Azure Docker **AWS** Kubernetes

EDUCATION

2021 - 2024

Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology BSc (Hons) in Information Technology Specializing in Software Engineering

HONORS & AWARDS

Winner

Haxmas 2021, SLASSCOM Ingenuity Awards 2021 - Best Innovative Product - LetMeKnow

Winner

Algothon 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present

Software Engineer - Spades App FZ-LLZ

Engage as a full-stack developer on multiple frontends and backends running as independent microservices

Development and maintainence of a full package ecosystem for Node.is microservices

Integrate with PSPs, cloud based POS systems and build a sustainable mechanism to gather data from closed systems through plug and play agents and browser plugins

Deploy and integrate with Apache Kafka on Kubernetes through helm and use it in combination with Azure Service Bus to maintain a steady communication flow between components

Write and deploy highly maintainable Azure functions

2021 - 2022

Software Engineer - Parallax Technologies

Active collaboration as a full-stack developer on multiple tech-stacks including Flutter, VueJS and Laravel

Design and develop a realtime notification system using NestJS, Socket.io and FCM

PROJECTS

Spades - Web based solution to revolutionize the dine in payment industry - https://www.spadesapp.io

Curfox DMS - Software for courier companies to build manage and grow their network - https://curfox.com

QickTeam - Mobile Application for individuals of similar interests to attend the same activity/event

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.teams_up

Bashaway - Fully fledged system for competitor registration, question/answer submission, progress analysis and marking. Made for Bashaway 2022 in collaboration with the

SLIIT FOSS Community - https://bashaway.sliitfoss.org

automatic-versioning - A NPM package which will automatically version an app in accordance with conventional commits. Made to work with monorepos to version just the updated workspaces

https://www.npmjs.com/package/automatic-versioning

mongoose-filter-query - A NPM package which standardizes a format for mapping an incoming http request's query params to a format which is supported by mongoose

https://www.npmjs.com/package/mongoose-filter-query

LetMeKnow - Mobile application and Web portal for the health care industry to actively monitor patients at an ICU

Covid Alert - Web portal and Mobile Application for marking and tracking Covid-19 patients with a real time notification and tracking system